handletheheat.com 2013-12-22

# Handle the Heat Privacy Policy »

We respect your privacy here at Handle the Heat. This Privacy Policy tells you what personal information is gathered when you visit this site and how that information is used for your benefit. Use of the Handle the Heat website is authorization of the information gathered to be used as detailed in this policy. 

Your personal information is not sold or shared for any purpose unless ordered by a court of law. 

The information collected on Handle the Heat is supplied by you from email notifications, commenting on the site, or viewing pages on the site. 

Like most websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. These include browser type, internet service provider, internet protocol addresses, referring and exit pages, platform type, time stamp, and the amount of clicks. 

We may use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can improve upon site experiences and tools in the future. You can decline cookies, though you may not experience all of the features of this site. We at Handle the Heat use third party advertisements to support the site. Some of these advertisers use technology such as cookies and web beacons (transparent image files used to track your journey on a website or collection of websites) when they advertise. This technology may allow advertisers to collect information including your ISP, IP address, browser, and your Flash capabilities. This information can be used for geotargeting or showing certain advertisements based on specific sites visited. However, this information is not personally identifiable. 

Handle the Heat contains links to external third-party sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of such sites. 

If you have submitted your personal information to Handle the Heat and would like it removed, please use [this contact form](http://www.handletheheat.com/contact). 

Handle the Heat reserves the right to modify, change, update, or add to this privacy policy at any time, immediately effective. Changes to the policy will be detailed on this page.

Updated January 10th, 2013.
